A Guide to the Records of Western State Hospital, 1825-2000
Library of Virginia
- Series III. Financial Records, 1838-1985., Extent: 5.675 cubic feet of records and 194 volumes.
  - Series III., Subseries C. Budget Records, 1927-1984.
    Contains a variety of budgetary documents including information on appropriations, expenditures and other state budget preparation material. The biennium budget for 1966-1968 is the focal point of much of the material. Included are mostly working papers and drafts of budgets and proposals submitted to the General Assembly. Additionally, one notable folder contains a 1927 letter from Governor Harry F. Byrd which discussed the need for all Virginia agencies to cut costs. Included in this folder is a study on consolidation and simplification of state government (Box 208, Folder 14). A Western State Hospital budget exhibit for 1970-1972 is located in Series II. Departmental and Program Records, Subseries A. Community Hospital Industrial Rehabilitation Program (CHIRP) Files, (Box 144, Folders 4-5). A 1982-1984 program exhibit for Western State is located in Series II. Departmental and Program Records, Subseries C. Shenandoah Geriatric Treatment Center (SGTC) Files, (Box 201, Folder 9). The budget records are part of accession 41404.
    Arranged alphabetically by subject.
    - Additional Costs for GO Form Budget ID, 1965-1966. (Box 204, Folder 1)
    - Additional Equipment, 1965-1966. (Box 204, Folder 2)
    - Analysis of the Budget, 1954-1956. (Box 204, Folder 3)
    - Appropriations and Expenditures, 1951-1953. (Box 204, Folder 4)
    - Biennial Budget Request, 1968-1970. (Box 204, Folder 5)
    - Biennial Budget Request (Medical Center), 1968-1970. (Box 204, Folder 6)
    - Biennium Budget, 1966-1968. (Box 204, Folder 7)
    - Biennium Budget, 1966-1968. (Box 204, Folder 8)
    - Biennium Budget, 1966-1968. (Box 204, Folder 9)
    - Biennium Budget, 1966-1968. (Box 204, Folder 10)
    - Biennium Budget, 1966-1968. (Box 204, Folder 11)
    - Biennium Budget, 1966-1968. (Box 204, Folder 12)
    - Biennium Budget, 1966-1968. (Box 204, Folder 13)
    - Biennium Budget, 1966-1968. (Box 204, Folder 14)
    - Budget Exhibit, 1950-1952. (Box 204, Folder 15)
    - Budget Exhibit, 1952-1954. (Box 204, Folder 16)
    - Budget Exhibit, 1954-1956. (Box 204, Folder 17)
    - Budget Exhibit, 1956-1958. (Box 205, Folder 1)
    - Budget Exhibit, 1960-1962. (Box 205, Folder 2)
    - Budget Exhibit, 1962-1964. (Box 205, Folder 3)
    - Budget Exhibit, 1962-1964. (Box 205, Folder 4)
    - Budget Exhibit, 1964-1966. (Box 205, Folder 5)
    - Budget Exhibit, 1964-1966. (Box 205, Folder 6)
    - Budget Exhibit, 1966-1968. (Box 205, Folder 7)
    - Budget Exhibit, 1966-1968. (Box 205, Folder 8)
    - Budget Exhibit, 1972-1974. (Box 205, Folder 9)
    - Budget Exhibit, 1972-1974. (Box 205, Folder 10)
    - Budget Exhibit, 1974-1976. (Box 205, Folder 11)
    - Budget Exhibit, 1974-1976. (Box 205, Folder 12)
    - Budget Exhibit, 1976-1978. (Box 205, Folder 13)
    - Budget Exhibit, 1976-1978. (Box 205, Folder 14)
    - Budget Exhibit, 1978-1980. (Box 206, Folder 1)
    - Budget Exhibit, 1978-1980. (Box 206, Folder 2)
    - Budget Exhibit (Lynchburg Training School and Hospital), 1968-1970. (Box 206, Folder 3)
    - Budget Exhibit (Lynchburg Training School and Hospital), 1968-1970. (Box 206, Folder 4)
    - Budget Exhibit (Lynchburg Training School and Hospital), 1968-1970. (Box 206, Folder 5)
    - Budget Manual for 1968-1970 Biennium, 1967. (Box 206, Folder 6)
    - Budget Request, 1952-1954. (Box 206, Folder 7)
    - Budget Request, 1966-1968. (Box 206, Folder 8)
    - Budget Requests / Supplementary Data (1948-1950), 1947. (Box 249, Folder 1)
    - Capital Outlay Program, 1972-1974. (Box 232, Folder 35)
    - Capital Outlay Reports, 1955-1964. (Box 206, Folder 9)
    - Capital Outlay Request, 1968-1970. (Box 206, Folder 10)
    - Charts and Memos, 1959. (Box 206, Folder 11)
    - Charts and Memos, 1960-1961. (Box 206, Folder 12)
    - Charts and Memos, 1963. (Box 206, Folder 13)
    - Charts and Memos, 1963. (Box 206, Folder 14)
    - Charts and Memos, 1963. (Box 206, Folder 15)
    - Charts and Memos, 1964. (Box 206, Folder 16)
    - Charts and Memos, 1964. (Box 207, Folder 1)
    - Charts and Memos, 1964. (Box 207, Folder 2)
    - Charts and Memos, 1964. (Box 207, Folder 3)
    - Charts and Memos, 1964. (Box 207, Folder 4)
    - Charts and Memos, 1964. (Box 207, Folder 5)
    - Charts and Memos, 1964. (Box 207, Folder 6)
    - Charts and Memos, 1964. (Box 207, Folder 7)
    - Charts and Memos, 1965. (Box 207, Folder 8)
    - Charts and Memos, 1965. (Box 207, Folder 9)
    - Charts and Memos, 1965. (Box 207, Folder 10)
    - Charts and Memos, 1965. (Box 207, Folder 11)
    - Charts and Memos, 1965. (Box 207, Folder 12)
    - Charts and Memos, 1965. (Box 207, Folder 13)
    - Charts and Memos, 1966. (Box 208, Folder 1)
    - Charts and Memos, 1966. (Box 208, Folder 2)
    - Charts and Memos (Food Service Department Survey), 1965. (Box 208, Folder 3)
    - Charts and Memos (Personnel Data), 1963. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Charts and Memos (Position Regrading), 1964. (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Charts and Memos (Printer's Copy), 1964. (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Charts and Memos (Quarterly Allotments), 1965. (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Charts and Memos (Summary of Positions and Salaries), 1964. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Charts and Memos (Work Copy), 1964. (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Expenditures, 1961-1963. (Box 208, Folder 4)
    - Expenditures, 1964-1965. (Box 208, Folder 5)
    - Financial Exhibit, 1980-1982. (Box 208, Folder 6)
    - Instructions for Budget Preparation and Presentation, 1961-1963. (Box 208, Folder 7)
    - Line Budget (Part 1), 1964-1965. (Box 208, Folder 8)
    - Line Budget (Part 2), 1964-1965. (Box 208, Folder 9)
    - Line Budget (Part 1), 1965-1966. (Box 208, Folder 10)
    - Line Budget (Part 2), 1965-1966. (Box 208, Folder 11)
    - Memorandums, 1967-1968. (Box 208, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous Documents, 1958-1967. (Box 208, Folder 13)
    - Organization and Management of the State Government of Virginia (Governor Harry F. Byrd letter), 1927. (Box 208, Folder 14)
    - Personal Services, 1965-1966. (Box 208, Folder 15)
    - Preliminary Budget Information (Library), 1964-1966. (Box 208, Folder 16)
    - Program Exhibit, 1980-1982. (Box 208, Folder 17)
    - Program Proposal, 1984-1986. (Box 232, Folder 36)
    - Reports on Audits, 1955-1959. (Box 208, Folder 18)
    - Reports on Audits, 1961-1966. (Box 208, Folder 19)
    - Working Budget Preparation, 1984. (Box 208, Folder 20)
    - Working Budgets, 1966-1969. (Box 208, Folder 21)
    - Workman Compensation Awards, 1964. (Box 208, Folder 22)
    - Workman Compensation Awards, 1965. (Box 208, Folder 23)
  - Series III., Subseries D. Expenditure and Purchasing Records, 1840-1985.
    Contains a wide variety of financial ledgers including account, cash, invoice, purchasing, receipt and wage payment books that document the cash flow at Western State Hospital. The ledgers document supply purchases made and often include information about what was purchased, from whom it was purchased, and the cost. Some of the volumes document the purchase of one particular item, such as coal or meat, while some reflect expenditures out of a particular account. Many of the ledgers in this subseries are missing bindings and other identifying information. The "Account Book (Miscellaneous)" category contains various order, purchasing, and general expenditure records which do not run in neat chronological order and may or may not be related to each other. Most of the accounting was handled by the steward, though these volumes could not be directly attributed to that position. Researchers may also benefit from reviewing the records of the Steward found in Subseries K. Steward's Records. The expenditure and purchasing records are part of accession 41404.
    Arranged alphabetically by type of record.
    - Account Book (Clothing), 1845-1849. (Volume 118)
    - Account Book (Coal), 1914-1915. (Volume 71)
    - Account Book (Contingent Fund), 1903-1925. (Volume 203)
    - Account Book (Contingent Fund), 1925-1928. (Volume 204)
    - Account Book (Support Fund), 1903-1911. (Volume 205)
    - Account Book (Daily Distribution of Collections), 1937-1940. (Volume 72)
    - Account Book (Geriatric Program), 1977-1985. (Volume 73)
    - Account Book (Ledger E), 1868-1897. (Volume 75)
    - Account Book (Miscellaneous), 1844-1858. (Volume 76)
    - Account Book (Miscellaneous), 1882-1884. (Volume 77)
    - Account Book (Miscellaneous), 1903-1913. (Volume 78)
    - Account Book (Miscellaneous), 1917-1933. (Volume 79)
    - Account Book (Miscellaneous), 1919-1924. (Volume 80)
    - Account Book (Miscellaneous), 1925-1934. (Volume 81)
    - Account Book (Miscellaneous), 1931-1934 [Also contains ward inventories, 1938-1939]. (Volume 82)
    - Account Book (Miscellaneous), 1939. (Volume 83)
    - Account Book (Miscellaneous), 1939-1940. (Volume 84)
    - Account Book (Miscellaneous), 1946. (Volume 85)
    - Account Book (Shoe Repair), 1840-1849. (Volume 74)
    - Cash Book, 1911-1920. (Volume 207)
    - Cash Book, 1923-1928. (Volume 86)
    - Cash Book (Special Appropriation Account), 1890-1898. (Volume 87)
    - Cash Book (Support Account), 1885-1901. (Volume 206)
    - Cash Receipts, 1903-1907. (Volume 88)
    - Invoice Book, 1905-1917. (Volume 89)
    - Invoice Book (Medical Office), 1894-1905. (Volume 90)
    - Meat Book, 1858. (Volume 91)
    - Order Book, undated, circa 1900-1910. (Volume 92)
    - Order Book, 1919. (Volume 93)
    - Order Book, 1920 [Also contains inventory of the gardener, 1928]. (Volume 94)
    - Order Book, 1922. (Volume 95)
    - Order Book, 1923-1924. (Volume 96)
    - Order Book, 1938. (Volume 97)
    - Order Book, 1938-1939. (Volume 98)
    - Order Book, 1938-1940. (Volume 99)
    - Order Book, 1939-1942. (Volume 100)
    - Order Book (Swift and Co. and Armour and Co.), 1920. (Volume 1040)
    - Purchasing Records, 1846-1882 [Also contains supply bid records, 1884-1890]. (Volume 101)
    - Purchasing Records, 1934-1935. (Volume 102)
    - Purchasing / Requisition Records (Printing, Binding, Stationery), 1912-1925. (Volume 103)
    - Purchasing / Requisition Records, 1944. (Box 209, Folder 1)
    - Purchasing / Requisition Records, 1944. (Box 209, Folder 2)
    - Purchasing / Requisition Records, 1944. (Box 209, Folder 3)
    - Purchasing / Requisition Records, 1944. (Box 209, Folder 4)
    - Purchasing / Requisition Records, 1946. (Box 209, Folder 5)
    - Purchasing / Requisition Records, 1946. (Box 209, Folder 6)
    - Purchasing / Requisition Records, 1946. (Box 209, Folder 7)
    - Purchasing / Requisition Records, 1946. (Box 209, Folder 8)
    - Purchasing / Requisition Records, 1946. (Box 209, Folder 9)
    - Purchasing / Requisition Records, 1946. (Box 209, Folder 10)
    - Purchasing / Requisition Records, 1946. (Box 209, Folder 11)
    - Purchasing / Requisition Records, 1946. (Box 210, Folder 1)
    - Purchasing / Requisition Records, 1946. (Box 210, Folder 2)
    - Purchasing / Requisition Records, 1946. (Box 210, Folder 3)
    - Purchasing / Requisition Records, 1946. (Box 210, Folder 4)
    - Purchasing / Requisition Records, 1946. (Box 210, Folder 5)
    - Purchasing / Requisition Records, 1946. (Box 210, Folder 6)
    - Purchasing / Requisition Records, 1946. (Box 210, Folder 7)
    - Purchasing / Requisition Records, 1946. (Box 210, Folder 8)
    - Purchasing / Requisition Records, 1946. (Box 210, Folder 9)
    - Purchasing / Requisition Records, 1946. (Box 211, Folder 1)
    - Purchasing / Requisition Records, 1946. (Box 211, Folder 2)
    - Purchasing / Requisition Records (Gas), 1946-1947. (Volume 104)
    - Purchasing / Requisition Records, 1948. (Box 211, Folder 3)
    - Purchasing / Requisition Records, 1948. (Box 211, Folder 4)
    - Purchasing / Requisition Records, 1948. (Box 211, Folder 5)
    - Purchasing / Requisition Records, 1948. (Box 211, Folder 6)
    - Purchasing / Requisition Records, 1948. (Box 211, Folder 7)
    - Purchasing / Requisition Records, 1948. (Box 211, Folder 8)
    - Purchasing / Requisition Records, 1948. (Box 211, Folder 9)
    - Purchasing / Requisition Records, 1948. (Box 211, Folder 10)
    - Purchasing / Requisition Records, 1948. (Box 211, Folder 11)
    - Purchasing / Requisition Records, 1948. (Box 212, Folder 1)
    - Purchasing / Requisition Records, 1948. (Box 212, Folder 2)
    - Purchasing / Requisition Records, 1948. (Box 212, Folder 3)
    - Purchasing / Requisition Records, 1948. (Box 212, Folder 4)
    - Purchasing / Requisition Records, 1948. (Box 212, Folder 5)
    - Purchasing / Requisition Records, 1948. (Box 212, Folder 6)
    - Purchasing / Requisition Records, 1948. (Box 212, Folder 7)
    - Purchasing / Requisition Records, 1948. (Box 212, Folder 8)
    - Purchasing / Requisition Records, 1948. (Box 212, Folder 9)
    - Purchasing / Requisition Records, 1948. (Box 212, Folder 10)
    - Purchasing / Requisition Records, 1948. (Box 212, Folder 11)
    - Purchasing / Requisition Records, 1948. (Box 212, Folder 12)
    - Purchasing / Requisition Records, 1948. (Box 213, Folder 1)
    - Purchasing / Requisition Records, 1948. (Box 213, Folder 2)
    - Purchasing / Requisition Records, 1949. (Box 213, Folder 3)
    - Purchasing / Requisition Records, 1949. (Box 213, Folder 4)
    - Purchasing / Requisition Records, 1949. (Box 213, Folder 5)
    - Purchasing / Requisition Records, 1949. (Box 213, Folder 6)
    - Purchasing / Requisition Records, 1949. (Box 213, Folder 7)
    - Purchasing / Requisition Records, 1949. (Box 213, Folder 8)
    - Purchasing / Requisition Records (General Supplies), 1949. (Volume 105)
    - Receipts and Disbursements, 1932. (Volume 106)
    - Receiving Reports, 1945-1946. (Volume 107)
    - Receiving Reports (Food), 1946-1947. (Volume 108)
    - Supply Bid Records, 1906-1908. (Volume 109)
    - Voucher Record, 1948-1950. (Volume 110)
    - Voucher Record, 1950-1951. (Volume 111)
    - Wage Book (Accounts with Special Attendants), 1841-1853. (Volume 112)
    - Wage Book, 1841-1884. (Volume 113)
    - Wage Book, 1872-1884 [Also contains account of supplies, 1884]. (Volume 114)
    - Wage Book (Ledger C), 1884-1893. (Volume 115)
    - Wage Book, 1894-1902. (Volume 116)
    - Wage Book, 1903-1908. (Volume 117)
  - Series III., Subseries E. Farm and Sewing Production Records, 1860-1945.
    Contains ledgers that document the goods produced by the onsite farming operations at Western State Hospital, as well as linens and clothing items sewn by female patients. It appears that the hospital used much of what it produced, but excess goods may also have been sold to the public. The farm and sewing production records are part of accession 41404.
    - Canning Record, 1935. (Volume 119)
    - Dairy / Milk Production Record, 1909-1916. (Volume 120)
    - Farm Ledger (Ledger for Farm), 1860-1880. (Volume 121)
    - Farm Ledger (Products of Farm), 1903-1908. (Volume 122)
    - Farm Report (Report of Farm and Garden), 1911-1912. (Box 214, Folder 1)
    - Farmer's Book, 1860-1867. (Volume 1021)
    - Occupational Therapy Sales Book (Sewing Items), 1942-1944. (Volume 1020)
    - Sewing Lists, 1939-1945. (Box 214, Folder 2)
    - Sewing Reports [Also contains patient expenditures and a recipe for paraffin], 1889-1893. (Volume 123)
    - Sewing Reports (Garments Made), 1917-1939. (Volume 124)
  - Series III., Subseries F. General Ledgers and Journals, 1884-1921.
    Contains accounting ledgers with information about Western State Hospital's general expense fund and its contingency fund. It is unclear whether the "contingent fund" and the "patient contingent fund" were separate accounts or one and the same. The money in the contingent account may have been patients' private funds. Journals accompany each ledger and contain daily or transactional accounts of money received and expended. The ledgers only contain final tabulations, often on a monthly basis. The ledgers and journals may have been kept by the Steward, since he controlled the hospital's day-to-day spending, and possibly the patients' private accounts as well. These volumes were separated from the other records of the Steward because of their unique labeling and the presence of separate journals. Gaps in time and alphabetical order remain unexplained. Researchers should review Subseries D. Expenditure and Purchasing Records, as well as Subseries K. Steward's Records for additional information. Those interested in private patient accounts should consult Subseries H. Patient Account Records. Additionally, two other volumes with similar labeling exist: "Ledger C" is a wage book located in Subseries D. Expenditure and Purchasing Records, "Ledger D, Contingent Account," which is located in Subseries H. Patient Account Records, and "Ledger E," which is an account book also located in Subseries D. Expenditure and Purchasing Records. It is unclear whether these volumes are part of the same alphabetical series as the ledgers found here. The general ledgers and journals are part of accession 41404.
    Arranged alphabetically by ledger letter.
    - Ledgers.
      - Ledger A, 1884-1902. (Volume 125)
      - Ledger B, 1907-1920. (Volume 126)
      - Ledger H (Contingent Fund), 1885-1891. (Volume 127)
      - Ledger K (Contingent Fund), 1891-1921. (Volume 128)
    - Journals.
      - Journal to Ledger A, 1884-1899. (Volume 129)
      - Journal to Ledgers A and B, 1899-1920. (Volume 130)
      - Journal to Ledger H, 1885-1890. (Volume 131)
      - Journal to Ledgers H and K, 1890-1897. (Volume 132)
      - Journal to Ledger K, 1897-1921. (Volume 133)
      - Journal to unidentified ledger, 1920-1923. (Volume 1041)
  - Series III., Subseries G. Indices (Miscellaneous), undated.
    Contains unidentified and undated financial indices indexed by company and individual names, or by type of supply. It is unknown whether these indices match up to other ledgers in this series. These indices are part of accession 41404.
    - Unidentified, undated. (Volume 134)
    - Unidentified, undated. (Volume 135)
    - Unidentified, undated. (Volume 136)
  - Series III., Subseries H. Patient Account Records, 1851-1957.
    Contains several ledgers and one folder of records that document how funds belonging to individual patients were handled. It appears that money was deposited by family members into accounts in order for patients to buy items not covered by the basic room and board provided by the hospital. Some patients also performed work for the hospital and were reimbursed through this method as well. The patient account ledgers are divided into three categories: account books, cash books (monies disbursed), and day books (monies received). Incoming funds were entered into the day books, outgoing funds were recorded in the cash books, and the account books contain both sets of information, arranged by patient name. Many of the account books contain indices because the entries are not usually arranged in alphabetical order. The second column of each transaction in the cash books contains the page number for the corresponding account book entry for that particular patient. One book of receipts for money paid to patient accounts through salaries or deposit by family members is also included in this suberies. Finally, amongst the ledgers is one file containing an annual report of patients' private funds for the years 1956-1957. Several of the volumes in this subseries refer to the "Patients' Contingent Account" or the "Contingent Fund." Researchers interested in patient funds and accounts information should also reference Subseries F. General Ledgers and Journals. Additionally, one ledger containing limited patient fund information for 1851-1853 can be found in Subseries K. Steward's Records, (Volume 201). The patient account records are part of accession 41404.
    Arranged alphabetically, then chronologically within.
    - Account Books.
      - 1851-1865. (Volume 138)
      - 1865-1878. (Volume 139)
      - 1878-1884. (Volume 140)
      - 1884-1889 (Ledger D, Contingent Account). (Volume 141)
      - 1889-1896. (Volume 142)
      - 1896-1901 (Individual Ledger, Patients' Contingent Account). (Volume 143)
      - 1901-1904. (Volume 144)
      - 1904-1908. (Volume 145)
      - 1908-1912. (Volume 146)
      - 1915-1929. (Volume 147)
      - 1915-1931. (Volume 148)
      - 1931-1936 (Male Patients). (Volume 176)
      - 1932-1936 (Female Patients). (Volume 177)
    - Annual Report.
      - Patients' Private Funds, 1956-1957. (Box 214, Folder 3)
    - Cash Books (Monies Disbursed).
      - 1885-1900. (Volume 149)
      - 1900-1903. (Volume 150)
      - 1903-1907. (Volume 151)
      - 1908-1911. (Volume 152)
      - 1911-1914. (Volume 153)
      - 1914-1915. (Volume 154)
      - 1915-1917. (Volume 155)
      - 1917-1920. (Volume 156)
      - 1926-1928. (Volume 157)
      - 1928-1929. (Volume 158)
      - 1929-1930. (Volume 159)
      - 1930-1932. (Volume 160)
      - 1932-1935. (Volume 161)
      - 1935-1936. (Volume 162)
      - 1939-1940. (Volume 163)
    - Day Books (Monies Received).
      - 1886-1888. (Volume 164)
      - 1889-1896. (Volume 165)
      - 1896-1905. (Volume 166)
      - 1897-1903. (Volume 167)
      - 1903-1904. (Volume 168)
      - 1905-1906. (Volume 169)
      - 1912-1921. (Volume 170)
      - 1921-1929. (Volume 171)
      - 1929-1931. (Volume 172)
      - 1930-1936. (Volume 173)
      - 1931-1936. (Volume 174)
    - Receipt Book.
      - 1946. (Volume 175)
  - Series III., Subseries I. Sales Books, 1894-1936.
    Contains information about goods sold by the hospital. The first two ledgers are linked chronologically and note money received and deposited, as well as who made the purchase, how much he or she paid, and where the money was deposited. Researchers should not that a ledger labeled "Steward's Sales," can be found in Subseries K. Steward's Records, (Volume 180). The sales books are part of accession 41404.
    - 1894-1897. (Volume 178)
    - 1897-1916. (Volume 179)
  - Series III., Subseries J. Special Funds Records, 1850-1958.
    Contains account books for several independent monetary funds set up to aid Western State Hospital patients. Most of the funds were set up by friends and family of current of former patients, with the money designated to pay for what were deemed "special comforts." These funds include the Murkland Fund, the Arlette McGiverin Fund, the Nathan H. Marshall Fund, and the Sallie V. and Elvira E. Chapman Fund. The origin of the Chapel Society is unclear, but its membership may have come from the hospital population, with the superintendent serving as treasurer. The last ledger contains receipts and disbursements for both the patient and special funds, but also the Commonwealth Fund which provided assistance to many rural hospitals. Several of the ledgers contain background information about the individual funds, sometimes in the form of correspondence. The special funds records are part of accession 41404.
    - Arlette McGiverin Fund, 1919-1936. (Volume 181)
    - Chapel Society (Account Book #2), 1850-1866. (Volume 182)
    - Murkland Fund, 1907-1936. (Volume 183)
    - Nathan H. Marshall Fund, 1932-1936. (Volume 184)
    - Patient and Special Funds (Misc.), 1921-1936. (Volume 185)
    - Patient and Special Funds (Misc.), 1951-1958. (Volume 186)
    - Sallie V. and Elvira E. Chapman Fund, 1934-1936. (Volume 187)
    - Special Comforts Fund, 1944-1949. (Volume 188)
    - Special Comforts Fund (Annual Report), 1956-1957. (Box 214, Folder 4)
  - Series III., Subseries K. Steward's Records, 1853-1936.